bopandtigerbeat.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy | BOP and Tiger Beat Online

**Share with your friends**

 **

  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use the Information 
  * Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
  * Cookies
  * Our Commitment to Security
  * How You can Access or Correct Information
  * How to Contact Us

**

****  
Thank you for visiting _BOP_ and _Tiger Beat_ Magazine Online, a Laufer Media, Inc. site. Your privacy is important to us.  
We will never sell or trade you or your child’s information to third-parties.

To better protect your privacy and that of your children, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your child’s information is collected and used at this Laufer Media, Inc. site. 

_BOP_ Magazine, _Tiger Beat_ Magazine and bopandtigerbeat.com are fully committed to complying with COPPA, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Our practices are outlined below. We urge kids under 13 in particular to check with their parents before entering information on any website and we urge parents to discuss with their kids restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don’t know.

Here is a list of the Laufer Media, Inc. business units  
governed by this privacy notice:

> _BOP_ and _Tiger Beat_ Online / BOPandTigerBeat.com   
>  _BOP_ Magazine / bopmag.com  
>  _Tiger Beat_ Magazine / tigerbeat.com 

**  
The Information We Collect**

At some Laufer Media, Inc. sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters or twitter feed. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

At some other Laufer Media, Inc. sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

back to top

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a “letter to our editors”), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.

Agents and contractors of Laufer Media, Inc. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Laufer Media, Inc.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. 

Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

back to top

**Privacy Options**

If you prefer not to receive traditional mail or other off-line promotions from this or any other Laufer Media, Inc. property or any companies not owned by Laufer Media, Inc., please ;?%3E/opt-out/%E2%80%9D%3Eclick%20here%3C/a%3E.%3C/p%3E%3Cp%3E%3Ca%20style=)If a Laufer Media, Inc. site discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Laufer Media, Inc. who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. Laufer Media, Inc. may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from this or any other Laufer Media, Inc. site, please back to top;?%3E/opt-out/%E2%80%9D%3Eclick%20here%3C/a%3E.%3C/p%3E%3Cp%3EFinally,%20Laufer%20Media,%20Inc.%20sites%20will%20not%20use%20or%20transfer%20personally%20identifiable%20information%20provided%20to%20us%20in%20ways%20unrelated%20to%20the%20ones%20described%20above%20without%20also%20providing%20you%20with%20an%20opportunity%20to%20opt%20out%20of%20these%20unrelated%20uses.%3C/p%3E%3Cp%3E%3Ca%20href=)

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Laufer Media, Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. Laufer Media, Inc. has no control over the third-party sponsors’ use of this information. The Laufer Media, Inc. site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

Laufer Media, Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). .

back to top

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These “web beacons” may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

back to top

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this Laufer Media, Inc. site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us by clicking [here](mailto:info@laufermedia.com).

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

back to top

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the Laufer Media, Inc. online policy for this site or its implementation please contact us via email by clicking [here](mailto:info@laufermedia.com) or at the following address:

_BOP_ and _Tiger Beat_ Online  
Attention: Customer Service  
330 N. Brand Blvd. Suite 1150  
Glendale, CA 91203 

back to top 

**Share with your friends**
